Veerendra Gangwar

Frontend developer

Email: virendragangwar88@gmail.com

Phone: 8285484247 Location: Noida

Summary

I worked as a UI/Front-end Developer at Skylabs Solutions India Pvt Ltd for 4 years, focusing on optimizing templates for load time and render-blocking JavaScript. I'm skilled in HTML/HTML5, CSS/CSS3, Bootstrap, W3.CSS, and Material Design, and have created various templates and emailers using Bootstrap (3, 4, 5) and Material Design.

Skills/Graphic Tools

HTML | CSS | HTML5 | CSS3 | BOOTSTRAP | MATERIALIZE CSS | JAVASCRIPT | JQUERY | Laravel | PHP | MYSQL | REACTJS | NextJs | NodeJs | Express Js | MongoDB

Work Experience

Skylabs Solutions India Pvt Ltd [Frontend / web developer]

Aug 2023 to June 2024

I worked as a front-end developer, designing over 7 projects using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap, as well as 2 projects using React.js and Laravel.

- Designed website using HTML CSS and Bootstrap in Laravel and React js.
- Created animation and JavaScript event to track user behavior.
- Optimized the website using current market tools and techniques.

Awarno [UI Developer]

January 2022 to July 2023

I have created more than 6 projects using HTML, CSS, and Bootstrap, and one project using Google Material Design.

- Designed website using HTML CSS and Bootstrap.
- Created animation and JavaScript event to track user behavior.
- Optimized the website using current market tools and techniques.

Optimization Toads [UI Designer]

Nov 2014 to March 2016

I have created more than 5+ projects using html css, bootstrap and design promotion mailer.

- Designed website using HTML CSS and Bootstrap.
- Designed promotion mailers.

Education

MCA Invertis university Bareilly UP	2021 (65%)
B.com MJPRU Bareilly UP	2018(53%)
12 th UP Board	2012(58%)
10 th UP Board	2010(51%)

Live URL's

Skylabs

http://promilpande.com | https://excelliaproperties.com | https://navishkar.com | https://healthandblossom.com | https://meradriver.com

Awarno

http://markmybrand.com | https://theluxuryflorett.com

React Projects

https://rayan88.netlify.app | https://veerendra-gangwar-portfolio.netlify.app

https://rasayankart88.netlify.app | https://v-ecom.netlify.app | https://v-com-tailwind.netlify.app/

https://vercel-test-ui.vercel.app/ | https://app-dashboard88.netlify.app/

Strength

Passionate to learn new technology, Quick learner, Disciplined & Optimistic

Personal Details

Father's Name : Mr. Hari Ram

Nationality : Indian Gender : Male Marital Status : Single

Date of Birth : 12th May 1995 Language Known : English, Hindi

I hereby declare that the information given above is true to the best of my knowledge.

Date: _/_/_

Place: Bareilly Veerendra Gangwar